AFL-CIO Internal Disputes Plan Decisions of the Impartial Umpire 5275
Kheel Center for Labor-Management Documentation & Archives
AFL-CIO Internal Disputes Plan Decisions of the Impartial Umpire
1953-1976
Kheel Center for Labor-Management Documentation & Archives
American Federation of Labor-Congress of Industrial Organizations (AFL-CIO)
5275
1 cubic feet
1 linear ft.
Records (documents).
This is a collection of decisions of the Impartial Umpire in AFL-CIO Internal Disputes.
5556133
General
Contact Information:
Kheel Center for Labor-Management Documentation and Archives Martin P. Catherwood Library 227 Ives Hall Cornell University Ithaca, NY 14853 (607) 255-3183> kheel_center@cornell.edu http://www.ilr.cornell.edu/library/kheel-center
Compiled by:
Kheel Staff, February 25, 2014
EAD encoding:
Randall Miles, February 23, 2017
Conditions Governing Access
Access to the collections in the Kheel Center is restricted. Please contact a reference archivist for access to these materials.
Cole, David L. (David Lawrence), 1902-1978; AFL-CIO; International Union, United Automobile, Aerospace, and Agricultural Implement Workers of America.; American Federation of Technical Engineers; Bricklayers, Masons, and Plasterers International Union of America; United Steelworkers of America; Brotherhood of Painters, Decorators, and Paperhangers of America; Retail Clerks International Association; Brotherhood Railway Carmen of the United States and Canada; Transport Workers Union of America; United Textile Workers of America; Communications Workers of America; International Association of Bridge, Structural, and Ornamental Iron Workers.; United Brotherhood of Carpenters and Joiners of America; International Brotherhood of Blacksmiths, Drop Forgers, and Helpers.; International Union, United Automobile, Aircraft, and Agricultural Implement Workers of America; Amalgamated Meat Cutters and Butcher Workmen of North America; United Packinghouse, Food, and Allied Workers; Amalgamated Clothing Workers of America; International Chemical Workers Union.; International Longshoremen's Association; American Bakery and Confectionery Workers' International Union.; Service Employees International Union; AFSCME; International Brotherhood of Firemen and Oilers; International Association of Machinists; Lithographers and Photoengravers International Union; Transport Workers Union of America; Air Line Pilots Association.; BRAC (Organization); American Train Dispatchers Association; United Cement, Lime and Gypsum Workers International Union; Retail, Wholesale, and Department Store Union; International Brotherhood of Electrical Workers; International Association of Machinists and Aerospace Workers.; Child Workers in Asia; Seafarers' International Union of North America.; Hotel & Restaurant Employees and Bartenders International Union.; Graphic Arts International Union; Aluminum Workers International Union; National Marine Engineers' Beneficial Association (U.S.); International Union of Operating Engineers; International Association of Marble, Slate and Stone Polishers, Rubbers and Sawyers, Tile and Marble Setters Helpers, Marble Mosaic and Terrazzo Workers Helpers.; Amalgamated Transit Union.; International Union of Electrical, Radio and Machine Workers; Laborers' International Union of North America; Newspaper Guild; American Federation of Television and Radio Artists; Office and Professional Employees International Union; United Shoe Workers of America; Brotherhood of Sleeping Car Porters; International Ladies' Garment Workers' Union; International Alliance of Theatrical Stage Employees and Moving Picture Machine Operators of the United States and Canada; International Union of Operating Engineers; United Paperworkers International Union; Sheet Metal Workers' International Association.; Bakery and Confectionery Workers' International Union of America.; Building and Construction Trades Council (Kansas City, Mo.); Lithographers and Photoengravers International Union.; International Printing Pressmen and Assistants' Union of North America; United Association of Journeymen Plumbers and Steam Fitters of the United States and Canada; Distillery, Rectifying, Wine and Allied Workers' International Union of America; American Federation of Government Employees; Office and Professional Employees International Union; United Paperworkers International Union; International Leather Goods, Plastics & Novelty Workers Union of America.; International Union of Doll and Toy Workers of the United States and Canada.; United Rubber, Cork, Linoleum, and Plastic Workers of America; Pattern Makers' League of North America.; Upholsterers' International Union of North America; United Glass and Ceramic Workers of North America.; Oil, Chemical, and Atomic Workers International Union; International Jewelry Workers Union; International Printing Pressmen and Assistants' Union of North America; United Furniture Workers of America.; Coopers' International Union of North America; Distillery, Rectifying, Wine and Allied Workers' International Union of America; International Alliance of Bill Posters, Billers and Distributors of the United States and Canada.; Brotherhood Railway Carmen of America; Communications Workers of America; International Chemical Workers Union.; Flight Engineers' International Association
5556133
- Cases and articles of various unions from the 60s and 70s (Box 1)
  - Major Labor Disputes, Re-Examination and Recommendations, 1953 (Box 1, Folder 1)
  - Report to the Director General on the Proposed Program for Improving Labor-Management Cooperation, 1955 (Box 1, Folder 2)
  - AFL-CIO Internal Dispute Plan, 1961 (Box 1, Folder 3)
  - AFL-CIO Internal Disputes Plan, Determinations, 1966-1967 (Box 1, Folder 4)
  - AFL-CIO Internal Disputes Plan, Index Digest, 1962-1967 (Box 1, Folder 5)
  - Determinations. Cases 63-85 through 64-110, not inclusive, 1964-1965 (Box 1, Folder 6)
  - Determinations. Cases 65-1 through 65-102, not inclusive, 1965-1966 (Box 1, Folder 7)
  - Determinations. Cases 66-9 through 66-133, not inclusive, 1966-1967 (Box 1, Folder 8)
  - Determinations. Cases 67-3 through 67-124, not inclusive, 1967-1968 (Box 1, Folder 9)
  - Determinations. Cases 68-1 through 68-117, not inclusive, 1968-1970 (Box 1, Folder 10)
  - Determinations. Cases 69-3 through 69-102, 1969-1970 (Box 1, Folder 11)
  - Determinations. Cases 70-2 through 70-109, not inclusive, 1970-1971 (Box 1, Folder 12)
  - Determinations. Cases 71-21 through 71-124, not inclusive, 1971-1972 (Box 1, Folder 13)
  - Determinations. Cases 72-7 through 72-134, 1972-1973 (Box 1, Folder 14)
  - Determinations. Cases 73-7 through 73-80, not inclusive, 1973 (Box 1, Folder 15)
  - Determinations. Cases 74-8 through 74-119, not inclusive, 1974-1975 (Box 1, Folder 16)
  - Determinations. Cases 75-2 through 75-107, not inclusive, 1975-1976 (Box 1, Folder 17)
  - Determinations. Cases 76-2 through 76-54, not inclusive, 1976 (Box 1, Folder 18)